I can't even protect myself.
how can I save all mankind?
That may be.
It's part of the plan.
A day with Shi Qiang
What do you want to do?
Right.
Mr. Luo Ji asked us to find
this exact place.
A dream.
What's hidden in people's heads
It's quite a lot.
If I said..
I wanted you to look for someone.
Can you do it?
what are you doing?
Waiting.
what are you waiting for?
It's useless.
This is the same.
After World War II
the form of spirit just disappeared from the army.
That's the traditional army
not space force.
Have you ever thought about how
Once you surrender and before you die.
How would Trisolarans treat human prisoners of war?
You are contradictory.
Mr. Tyler.
Yes?
You are skeptical about the outcome of the war.
I'm here to avoid losing the war.
and yet you are convinced that I can find
something that doesn't exist.
This is the only way I can help you.
Mr. Tyler
Humanity
Won't fail.
Hello Mr. Tyler
associate Director of the Wallfacer Project.
Bog Doyle.
What is the diameter of the macroelectron in the grounded state?
20 cm
Not enough.
No way that
it can only be excited by energy level.
What do you mean?
What is not enough?
This is the alternate abort procedure
Can restore the ball lightning to a low-level energy state
to ensure the safety of the experimental process.
Throw it out.
I want a weapon
and you talk to me about safety.
The safest thing to do is to do nothing
if there is a problem with the experiment.
Mr. Tyler.
I have to contact the PDC.
This has nothing to do with you.
Let's not talk about safety, ok?
Good.
when I stimulate the macroelectrons to
highest energy state
its waves cover the entire target area
Is it enough?
Isn't that how it should have been?
It is correct.
Wait.
Electrons are subatomic particles..
You have all operated at this level.
Dr. Dingyi's microscopic lock.
Macroelectrons.
Electrons on a macroscopic scale
that are visible to the naked eye
require special calibration tools.
That's why we came all the way here.
Compared to the naked eye
the optical detection system used in B3436 experiments
is needed to see them more clearly.
60 degrees southeast.
3mm
Done.
Stop.
This is the Lethal Weapon's baby state.
It won't be any threat.
Macroelectrons have been released.
Don't worry.
Radiation detected.
Confirm that the macrolectron is in a stable state.
Right now it's only an empty bubble.
and the diameter of the channel is 13.6 meters.
Verify levitation.
Motion limited to a 67.9 cm radius.
But as far as I know
Ball lightning
can't be limited by physical barriers.
how is it contained?
It has a certain amount of negative charge
and can only bound by one thing.
A magnetic field.
Of course I know that.
That's fine.
We tested the magnetic field strength
50,000 bionic dynamic magnets here
have full control over the speed of the ball lightning.
Acceleration zone magnetic traction test.
The same principle applies to space elevators.
Increment the magnetic force.
Applied voltage has reached 100 million volts.
The magnetic field has covered the target area.
Acknowledged.
What
This is too primitive.
This is..
Obsidian.
This is just stone.
You spent billions
The target
is designed according to the physical data model.
It contains all known elements on earth
in a stable form to prevent reactions
and the inside
forms a polycrystalline structure
The wave front created in the instant of collision
will leave traces in the detection area.
This is important data for building a model of the ball lightning weapon.
If it were merely a rock
then we're just merely carbohydrates.
Such an expensive experiment
what if it fails?
There is always a one in ten thousand possibility.
Impossible.
Any results are good results.
What we want to see
That is, after hitting this collection of elements
what will happen?
During the moment of contact
what if the elements react again?
They will not.
Ball lightning is faster than them.
But you just said
Macroelectrons is slow.
Macroelectrons needs artificial lightning for excitation.
Only then will it have all the attributes of a quantum state weapon.
That can be called
ball lightning.
The old equipment at the base of the B436 project
has been restored
but it still requires you to provide the key for the core components.
Leave it alone
Let us head into the laboratory.
Have you checked the parameters of the high-speed camera?
No problems.
Enough to slow down the experiment process by a factor of 1.5 million.
Mr. Tyler.
Doctor.
Surveillance system checked.
Ok.
Mr. Tyler.
Please follow me.
The test data is stable.
The Experiment is ready to begin.
Begin recording.
7:00 a.m.
Instrument calibration complete.
Please confirm.
Who is speaking?
Voiceprint confirmed.
The excitation area is ready to start.
It is the previous experiment leader
but don't know who.
That person
Where are they now?
Please begin.
Macroelectrons process initiated.
Macroelectrons storage state is stable.
Location set.
Superconducting terminal battery is negative.
The superconducting wire is connected
Ready.
Start the macroelectrons process.
Macroelectrons and the electromagnetic rail are ready.
Lightning ready.
Ready.
300 kA
600 kA
800 kA
Ball lighthning excitation completed.
The precession path is stable.
The ball lightning has jumped to a high energy state.
Success.
Don't relax yet.
Correct the magnetic field strength in the target area.
Sorry doctor.
What happened?
Was there a power outage?
or a device failure?
Doctor.
The energy value of the target area has returned to normal.
Restart the monitoring system.
Doctor.
I don't know how..
I cleaned the target area.
Don't speak.
It's useless.
It's all over now.
Are the experiment results still valid?
Polluted.
I'm sorry.
Give me another 7 days.
please.
It's useless to give you another 7 years
if you don't have the capability.
An utter waste.
You are
only holding me back.
Uh..
Mr. Tyler applied for
the next space experiment budget.
just do as he says.
OMEN Shadow Elf 8 Pro
Please sit.
Hello
My name is Luo Ji.
Mr. Luo Ji, The water pipe broke.
The decoration team can't come.
We must make a satellite phone call to the PDC now.
OK, OK, you can figure it out.
Don't call me if the water pipe breaks.
It doesn't concern me.
Hello.
Excuse me.
You are..
Is it Mr. Luo?
She's talking to you.
I am Luo Ji.
Hello.
You two talk.
I'll go check it out.
Hello Mr. Luo.
My name is Yan
Professor Luo?
Miss Yan.
Hello.
Sit, please sit.
My name is Zhuang.
Professor Luo
Just call me Zhuang Yan
Zhuang Yan.
Sorry.
I am sorry.
Have some tea.
Thank you.
Oh, right.
I almost forgot.
Are you cold
perhaps?
I'll light the fireplace right away.
I thought
you would be very fierce
every moment
and throw things like this
No no no..
no.
You misunderstand.
I was..
I know.
This is sudden.
Right.
A bit sudden.
Oh, right.
Say..
What did you..
think I would look like?
It's nothing.
Say whatever you think.
I thought you would
stand in front a map every day
and point at a bunch of people in uniform.
Come on..
I'm not like that.
Then I thought about
what kind of work you might arrange for me.
Work.
Oh, right.
You are a student.
learning to draw.
Right?
The last cohort of students of the Qingyun Academy of Fine Arts
Last cohort?
The professor said..
painting in this era
is useless.
Professor Luo
What do you think?
How could that be possible? Zhuang Yan.
What you need to know is
that in this era especially
there should be something that nourishes the heart.
Did you know
Goethe said
that his beloved..
What kind of bird language?
Is it an angle grinder or a vertical drill?
Can you straighten your tongue?
You!
About what Goethe said..
At that time he said
why are you yelling?
I know where to find you.
The Excavator is here.
I will dig up the graves for eight generations of your ancestors.
Jerk.
Really..
I'm furious.
What did you say
Mr. Luo Ji?
Jeez.
Wait for me
I'll drive the excavator
right over the top of your head.
They are fixing the plumbing.
What did the PDC say?
Professor Luo
are you ok?
I'm ok.
Would you like some red wine?
Sure..
Only us.
where were we?
Goethe.
Right.
Yes.
You can escape from this world
through art
in a more reliable way.
That..
is the allure of art.
Say..
Can I continue to draw?
Of course you can.
Zhuang Yan.
Believe me.
No matter how the world changes.
In here
art and beauty
come first.
So in here
you..
come first.
Brother Luo, I think..
you guys should go outside and talk.
The house is falling down.
Professor Luo
do you have something to say?
Nothing.
I just want to ask you.
Do you like it here?
But don't answer now.
I love it.
Really?
Look.
It looks like
the eyes of sunset.
The sky here is different from anywhere else
it's very open.
I feel that too
like in
the north pole.
or..
don't say.
I do not want to know.
Why?
As soon as I know where I am
the world seems smaller.
I see.
Actually
I do not know either.
really?
except now you are here
I do not want to know anything.
Brother Luo.
Dinner.
I'm coming.
How have you been feeling recently?
I did what you said
But it's getting worse.
You say love
but..
This is serious.
What else?
Or
how you feel..
What made you feel this strongly?
One day
I saw her in the library
and she
smiled at me a little.
You mean
she is real?
Yes.
No.
You could say
she is more than real.
Please relax.
It's ok if you don't want to say.
I do not know what to say.
For example
in your novel.
How did you imagine her when you wrote it?
why do you think
you developed feelings for her?
what are your thoughts?
Go ahead.
I used to think
The characters in a novel are controlled by the author.
But that's not true.
It's almost the opposite.
I can feel her presence.
I can feel it all around me.
I can feel it bit by bit
and see the outline of her life.
I imagine a rainy day
everyone is in a hurry.
But then I see.
She takes a leisurely walk in the rain.
She suddenly puts away the umbrella.
.
She Enjoys the feeling of twirling in the rain.
She Enjoys the feeling of being in contact with the rain.
I also imagined her closet.
The color and style of each garment.
her song preference.
the movies she likes.
and what's on her dresser.
and how she doesn't need makeup.
The way she was born is best.
most beautiful.
and sometimes
She is there
sitting in the clasroom.
Wearing a beige turtleneck sweater
she smiles at me.
It's like..
like the sun rising after a snowstorm.
Oh..
I can't go on like this.
How can you give all your feelings to a ghost?
How can I?
Please be serious.
This is serious.
I am in love with a
person who doesn't exist.
a fantasy and yet,
I live with her.
You also said
Just because she doesn't like the smell of cigarettes.
I don't know what to do.
as long as
she is there for me
I feel very happy too.
I am satisfied.
I know everything is fake
I can never touch her
but i will never forget her.
Don't forget
about why you are here.
is this ok?
Just don't resist the people around you
let nature take its course.
Her influence on you will become less and less
actually you can think of it this way
Whether she really exists or not
your love
is real to you.