control center please answer
Ghost 1
Moving towards the ladder
please answer
give up docking
Measure the speed of the target ship
dad
alarm
Damage to the main structure of the No. 2 Gravity Port in Gaokong Yihuan was detected
The gravity system of the high-altitude ring is about to be paralyzed
All personnel are ready for weightlessness and anti-collision
Alert High Altitude Third Ring Well No. 4 was broken down
Massive explosion on alarm truss
Alert Spaceport Debris Chain Reaction
Alert of major structural damage to space dock
The main structure of the alarm space repair factory disintegrated
Alert all personnel to stop work
Go to the emergency assembly point
Space station hit by space debris
what's the matter
strong chain reaction
stop moving
Mandatory locking of low-altitude station dock platform
what about that
Ladder carrying cabins are locked across the board
first time this happened
All transportation and resupply operations terminated
what's the situation
Where did the pieces come from?
Repeat for all personnel to stop operations
listen to the radio
Who are you not at the high altitude station
go to the rendezvous point
Why is my badge in yours?
take me to the control room
quickly
No, the control room is now
What nonsense
wallfacer on top
quick
OK
come with me
here
Alarm fiber optic data transceiver terminal is impacted
Alert all occupants to evacuate quickly
Stay away from dense areas of space debris
Central axis power shortage
Regular lighting suspended
Some auxiliary functions suspend power supply
A team arrives at the three-dimensional traffic hall
receive
Wireless communication is only possible for short distances
Maintain the positioning between spacesuits at all times
Be careful not to fall behind
clear
This is where the hatches are the most damaged
Be safe when patching
clear
What's this
This is
The high-altitude ring gravity system has been restored
F ring road G ring road
Cabin pressure below emergency limit
All people stay away
Or force open the airtight door
Damaged solar cell wings
Battery pack failure
The power system has switched to emergency mode
Are you OK
Come
no helmets
Fortunately it's okay
young people are so-so
thanks
I didn't expect my old Miao to be so lucky.
let's go
This is
Where to
go wallfacer
What are you doing here?
My old Miao has never cheated anyone in my life
rest assured
Come
Waiting for the rescue team?
When will you wait?
No signal to the ground
Come
don't touch your head
Thank you Master Miao
You're welcome
The upward fiber is not broken
But there is only the Yellow River Station with counterweight on it
How hard should you be?
this little arm
go back and practice more
good for health
chairman
The wired and wireless communication of the high-altitude station is completely cut off
Only the returned data before losing contact
We are trying to observe remotely
But nearby satellites also
How is the damage?
The truss exploded
The bottom fiber optic cable is damaged
Resulting space debris is being tracked
some will burn up in the atmosphere
No
i mean the top of the sky station
Luo Ji's position appeared there
Is this where the spaceship hit?
what about images
Urgently transferred satellites in other orbits to the past
Cone of light in high orbit is changing orbit
but it will take a long time
good
We need to know what's going on inside as soon as possible.
is there a way to go up
Allows low-altitude stations to launch
they are close
Isn't Officer Shi right there?
no
The low-altitude station is also lost.
And an air crash triggers their security lock
The spaceship can't move
The Ministry of space can transfer three aerospace planes in close proximity
go straight in
The fastest way so far
and the only
chairman
This is impossible
What's wrong
that is
The signal near the high-altitude station disappeared instantly
above
It's like suddenly adding a transparent cover
wireless signal is gone
shouldn't
The aircraft can't detect it either.
Such a large range of electromagnetic environment
how was it destroyed
what's up
Who are you
how to enter
you stop
Yang Gong
They belong to the Ministry of Defense and Security of the Earth
Responsible for the safety of the Wallfacers
Has the Yellow River Station also lost contact?
No
But that's an empty nuclear power plant
what is this
You come
have you contacted
email sent
but no one answered the call
keep playing
strangeness
Mid-cut Infrared Observation
what is this
have no idea
Try it with an Imaging Spectrograph
Radio observations can't penetrate blind spots.
reset aiming system
no no no no
How can I see the high-altitude station clearly?
16,000 kilometers apart
The aiming system has reached its limit
Did the PDC have instructions?
keep trying to contact
But there is always a problem with the communication
Yang Gong
The upper and lower optical fiber signals are definitely broken
what happened
I'm going to check the communication module
Dr. Ding
I'll make a long story short
No
You can just worry about the ladder
i have to say something more serious
The satellite has previously received full band information
Roughly the content is that the ball lightning capture ship is out of control.
Yaw towards the ladder
chairman
I apply for a small-scale disclosure of project information B436
allow
Thanks
I tried to deduce what just happened when I got off the ladder
It should be directly related to ball lightning
So here's what I'm going to say
will exceed everyone's understanding
but i'll try to make it clear
Ball Lightning will choose a target to attack
Spectrum ball flash
only attack one target
Just to ask
Is the main body of the ladder still there?
Of course
that could be worse
What's the meaning
Currently recognized spectrum of ball flash
only two
at the molecular level
For biological DNA and inorganic substances respectively
if the ladder is still there
That means the ball flashes
It is likely to attack the human body
reportable display
This ball flash just destroyed the target
yes
But the spectrum has definitely been rewritten
Although I don't know how it works
that time
survivor on the ladder
should be its goal
what will happen to them
Professor Wang
you should have guessed
Humans will resonate with the ball flash
quantized by it
in the information she left
just wrote this
But the truth is definitely more complicated
Will those quantized people disappear?
this problem
i can't answer you directly
There is likely to be a macro universe in our world
so
Macromatter will be randomly distributed in space
I have participated in the capture of macronuclei in North China before
now born on the ladder
It should be a macroelectronics
The moment of reaction with the human body
combined with a macro nucleus
A complete macro system formed spontaneously
I call it quantum body for the time being
no
If a new system is created
Then why didn't Mr. Taylor's ground experiment last time
Like you said
the ground will not have
space station in space
Exposure to extremely low temperature after damage
Under this premise
Particle thermal motion is minimized
can only move in a limited space
combine with each other
bound state
There is a system to speak of
But no matter which quantum state
At the macro level, it is also fundamentally
cannot exist stably
Is it right
pity the world
not as simple as in the book
Countless sophons are watching us
Whether the observer effect is strong or weak
will maintain the stability of this quantum body
make it retain its quantum nature
and can pose a constant threat to us
that for us
what this threat means
you can understand
Ball lightning breaks down the boundary between macro and micro
quantum body
like a mold
Infected our macrocosm
once it starts expanding
The whole space generates what we don't understand
Uncontrollable mutations
so you're saying
The real disaster has just begun
Is it right
I can only say
wish we had time
Redundancy check completed
just checked
Terminal is restarting
Please return personnel from extravehicular operations to conduct radioactive testing as soon as possible
Will soon be able to communicate with the ground
old yang look
There are aircraft near the high-altitude station
Has the PDC come to the rescue?
But the satellite signal didn't come back
How can we wait to save lives?
As soon as the platform is unlocked, let's hurry up
chairman
The rescue ship has arrived
connect now
receive
What's wrong
There seems to be something wrong with the attitude of the spaceship
No. 2 navigation system failure
Unable to avoid obstacles
Toggling manual operation
Here is the measurement and control
observe the surrounding environment
Be aware of collision risk
No. 1 power distribution fault
propulsion system failure
watch out for debris
emergency avoidance
it's too late
Low-altitude station communication has been restored
Sky Ladder Flight Control Center
This is Yang Jinbiao
communication just resumed
we filmed the crash
chairman
What should we do now
Stand by first
Might have found a clue
chairman
I offline first
I think
There is always a way out
It's fine
That
How do we get back to the ground?
Come back as you come
Downward facing fiber is broken
but nanosilk is alright
otherwise
The ladder is down
rest assured
The alert didn't say the capsule was damaged.
Don't count on waiting for rescue.
Ride along the central axis
I will take you down
Meet the PDC Chairman
Remember to mention it to her
This is my job number
remember
Okay
say what you want
didn't think about it
talk later
girl
Please look around for a supply pack
we use it on the road
good
No
I go
she stays here
You have to cooperate with me to pull this thing
strong enough
i know where
I will be back soon
Continue to calculate the landing point of the escape pod in real time
All follow-up rescues that went up were withdrawn.
What's the meaning
chairman
Can't help?
regular rescue doesn't work
No need to put more people at risk
Is Ding Yi still okay?
no news yet
chairman
he came
my side
Ding Yi
is there any solution though say
This resource can be called
there is no way
But this wireless communication blind spot is a bit of an eye-opener.
give me split screen
receive
Electron orbital diagram of hydrogen atom
you got it wrong
No
this one
Use it as an analogy to this newly born quantum body
I guessed before
After the ball flash spaceship lost control
The moment of reaction with the human body
with a stable macronucleus
formed this new system
sounds a bit complicated
But this structure is theoretically
It is similar to the hydrogen atom diagram in the middle school textbook
how to verify
Isn't the particle experiment aborted?
unable to verify
But it's probably right
because that's the only way
just makes sense
ready to pull
What
Master Miao
What did you say
I said
No problem with the traction machine and the guide rail
we can go up
are you ready to wind up
good
pull it now
Master Miao
PhD
now is not the time to take chances
certainly
but the word probability
This is the biggest difference between the quantum world and us
over there
all possibilities exist
and at the same time
The quantum body is a bound state like a hydrogen atom
We can follow the probability density
that is, the degree of danger to people
Divide it into several layers of energy zones
The further you go, the more dangerous
The spaceship just now should be
Inadvertently touched the outermost layer of the quantum body
outer layer
That's where the rescue ship went out of control.
Yes
start here
The turbulent magnetic field forms a shielding network
Not only isolates the wireless signal
can also damage electronic equipment
completely disconnect us from the people inside
if
if someone is alive
you want to ask
Will it "die"
Is it right
tell me first
what do you think death is
stop breathing
no heartbeat
then you said die
Nothing in the quantum world
in the microscopic dimension
It can only be said that all the particles that make up a person
probability of their existence
amortized infinitely
diffusion
until you in the macro dimension
completely broken down into elementary particles
Therefore, when people face the quantum body
destroy
It should have happened unconsciously
But from a scientific point of view
destroy the word
not accurate
because there is nothing
really ruined
The momentum of matter is still there
Angular momentum is still
like a deck of cards
Still 54
It's just a reshuffle
but life
It's a straight flush
such a wash
nothing is gone
Gone
do you mean the people above
You just said that this quantum body has many energy regions
different levels of danger
right
outermost shield
It's what you call a wireless communication blind spot.
Doesn't do much harm to people
But covering the entire high-altitude station
make it impossible for us to go in and rescue
Innermost is the core area
highest probability density
deadliest to survivors
are these your guesses
clue left by a friend
I can probably understand her metaphor
We have worked together on the B436 project
so
humans in this area
hell
More thorough than death in the ordinary sense
mesosphere
I call it the consciousness layer
The probability density is not so high
if anyone is alive
maybe it's here
the person in the quantum body
Will you see a probability cloud visible to the naked eye?
Probability clouds are arguably not seen
because observation causes the cloud to collapse
but this time
observer inside it
maybe an exception
in it
so-called space-time
will be fleeting like a bubble
If survivors fail to pass observation
Collapse the probability cloud
his own macroscopic existence
will decay infinitely
this process
will be as natural as ice melting into water
my eyes
what's wrong with my eyes
no
i can't die here
Zhuang Yan is still waiting for me
I'm more worried about
High-speed motion of macroelectronics
would cause very strong gravitational disturbances
In this case
Quantum near
It's like laying out a
The gravitational net that almost only locks the spectrum of the human body
Even if the survivors can temporarily hide in a safe area
There is no way to avoid the influence of gravity
What
Once the macrograviton starts to fluctuate
eventually all of the above
will be captured by the quantum body
what happened
what the hell
its own existence
not for a particular person
but because the spectrum corresponds to
you are within its bounds again
It's hard not to be affected by the entire energy hierarchy
Why am I the only one upside down
wrong
this is not normal gravity
And in this process
People are like Schrödinger's cat, which is both alive and dead
Slowly evolve into a superposition state
If many I stack together
You can see objects in multiple spaces at the same time
No way
if one of i is mirrored
the traces that I saw and left
will also be mirrored
what happened
completely determined by probability
what the hell
This is impossible
it's unreasonable
This is a space that breaks the rules of classical physics
But it's not that time and space have changed
but
Many parallel time and space overlap or expand at a certain position
Is it a matter of space?
If using astronomical observation methods
Assume the celestial body is 0 degrees
time angle with right ascension
I want to see
true hour coordinates
It looks like the horizon is below
and perpendicular to gravity
above is the zenith
I just need to find the extension point of the plumb line
3 sidereal hours
45 degree hour angle
that right ascension position
viewing angle equal to
right?
or am i missing something
light refraction
gravitational source
corrected altitude
Or am I assuming the wrong location?
do not care
Ruined
no angle is normal
fine
i want to calm down
there is always a way
I have to take Zhuang Yan away
there must be a way
take a deep breath
there must be a way out
just find the pattern
i can't die here
But you said that sophon surveillance allows the quantum
At least part of it is in a stable state
Can humans survive in the same way?
you say the observer effect
yes
theoretically possible
I can only say
If all probabilities exist there
anything is possible
There might be a one in a million chance
is a miracle happened
what happens
what's wrong with your eyes
fine
Walk
Don't you want something?
I have been looking for a long time
Where's Master Miao?
don't look back
go quickly
In the end what happened
Is it Master Miao?
What will happen to this quantum body in the end?
If it doesn't stop it from spreading
our world
It's just a still three-dimensional lake.
The quantum body is like throwing a stone on the water
The more particles it absorbs
The phase space of the quantum state that needs to be maintained is larger
at last
The calm of the entire lake will be broken
No matter how deep the ladder is
no difference
anyway sooner or later
will be occupied by waves of the quantum state
Shelter fire alarm has been lifted
what happened
Please enter carefully
Where is the master?
Repair as soon as possible
you close the door
how did he get in
High-altitude station ring road 1 and ring road 2 were seriously damaged
Is it the elevator shaft that hasn't been repaired?
still
we are going to split up
Isolated from the rest of the ring
even if i can't help
at least tell me
let me know what's going on
Now the compartments here are all locked.
let me help you
Need not
now it's just the two of us
gotta go
In addition to the internal service signal
No other survivors detected
Please be careful
Regulate the use of escape equipment
Luo Ji
don't do this
alright
Remember this red button
used for launch
just press it
this is a bit of pure water
but not much
Should be enough for when you're waiting for rescue
what would you do
there is only one
When it is ten kilometers above the ground, it will open a parachute
No matter where you land after that
will automatically send a beacon
PDC can receive ij
In case of danger after landing
no
If you want to go, you go
your safest
my safety is none of your business
Do you know what's going on now?
That Lao Miao
I can't even tell if he's dead or not.
Didn't you just keep saying you were leaving?
I let you go now and you don't go
what else do you want
what are you dissatisfied with
I'm not dissatisfied
I appreciate it
you figured it out
I ask you as a wallfacer
i am ordering you
Roll as far as you can
Laying here doesn't make any sense
PDC has to listen to me
why don't you listen
Right
remember
except pressing this button
just click
don't touch anything else
Helmet?
there
circulatory system here
Fully protects you until a safe landing on the ground
you do not need
Escape pod launched successfully
i pressed
Listen to you
if this is the last view
not bad
Is it right
Yes Dashi
I'm really blinded by you
i always wanted to ask