Renshougong
Shiyun Al J
be the first to break
you are admirable
Been a Wallfacer for so long
you
It must be difficult
looking for someone
I have a way
Have you heard of the Beacon Tower?
Luo Ji
There are only about 8 hours left until the ladder is fully covered
It is impossible to break free from gravity directly
Only by being thrown out by force
do one's best
Luo Ji
listen to fate
wake up
The current barometric pressure is stable
here
arrive
what's on your mind
I'm thinking
It's pitch black in the helmet
Is this the true face of the universe?
everything is uncertain
are filtered out
only see numbers
Coordinate System
do you wish so
do not wish
Why
then i can't see you
Why do you have to see me?
I feel at ease seeing you
when you look at me
did i just collapse
According to Dr. Ding
you don't think
Collapse means disappear
Nope
Isn't the quantum body always there?
don’t worry
I won't let anything happen to you
I seem to have dreamed about this scene
floating in space
No
floating in the sea
Feeling like a fish thrown into the ocean when I graduate
don't know where to go
but now
never so clear
what do you know now
this has oxygen
The helmet can be removed
Prompt that the helmet has been removed
know what we are going to do
First go to the spindle console
release nanofilaments
Raise the Yellow River Station
Right
Then what
Turn on the nuclear power plant that is going to fly away to the maximum
In this way, the quantum body will run up in a short time
until the nuclear power plant took it away
Let's hurry back at this time
back here
right
no
no no no
so can't do it
What's wrong
it's worse than the outer ring
The backup battery can't even open the cabin door.
How is it possible to release nanofilaments
PDC is not cheating, is it?
what to do
Don't nuclear power plants have electricity?
Then you have to put nanowires first and then run the nuclear power plant.
or
Reverse the order of operations
Generate electricity first and then let the Yellow River station rise
but in this case
can we get back here safely
I have no idea
to two
bomb
on the tube
don't want
Do not want any
--H+-- two
cities one
gone again
Captain Shi, are you cheating?
don't moan
face stretched out
Lumpy
guard
yes
it's me
Cantor
here to send you the files
part of the plan
this kid
Give me another life
quick
Hurry up
coming
Changan Deep Blue first reaches the future
how long has passed
10 minutes later than expected
It stands to reason that the nuclear power plant will automatically disengage when it detects the altitude
but now it's completely unresponsive
Rescue?
Once the platform is unlocked, you can go
But we have to wait for Luo Ji to finish the last step
The backup battery is almost gone.
We need to start the nuclear power plant quickly
Wireless communication is only possible for short distances
We can't lose touch anymore
The essence of the observer effect is the outflow of information
outflow of information
information
In case the quantum body gets close
you remember
you turn on visual enhancement mode
Didn't you say that visual enhancement should not be touched?
but it occurred to me
Visual enhancements and extravehicular suit data
Isn't it essentially our message?
Ding Yi said before
Must establish a stable connection between us and outside the shield
If short distance wireless
plus long-distance fiber
Let the Yellow River Station receive our information
Are you going to use what Dr. Ding said?
quantum observer effect
This classmate is very smart
Teacher Luo also teaches very well.
This may be the only way to survive in the quantum body
you still stay here
don't go anywhere
do you know
i stay here
Wait a moment
Why
what are you doing
we can't be apart
i told you
promise me first
I know
I remember every word you say
including unspoken
you don't want me in danger
Is it right
So someone has to do it
Otherwise we can't go
i'm not leaving you alone
After the quantum body is close
I can't tell the direction
so you gotta be mine
my lighthouse
I can't come back without location
you have to wait for me here
guide me
okay
you want to come back
You still have something to give me
Say no to the one who will regret it
A|^r Zq^r
you saw it
you mean
Do you want to
I'm still waiting for you to tell me
what did goethe say
this
that's what you said
don't regret it
when i come back
you can't lie to me
as long as you come back
You are
I'm right there
Abnormal increase in ionizing radiation detected
Abnormal increase in magnetic field strength
come so fast
How are you
It was magnetic interference just now
fine
I'm fine
to the control area of ​​the central axis
then I will not bother you
Don't
I feel at ease listening to your voice
what are you laughing at
Actually me too
Wait a moment
Zhuang Yan
I am here
what i do now
If you go back, you have to testify for me.
PDC taught me
Would someone ask Wallfacer that?
Yes
It's definitely part of the plan
really
normal operation doesn't work at all
same as i thought
We must first build a nuclear power plant
then you protect yourself
Is full power dangerous?
nothing
just follow the directions
there is no other way
i started
don't don't don't don't
what are you doing
What's the matter? Luo Ji
Luo Ji
don't talk
I am anxious
Zhuang Yan
I'm telling you
nothing
or just
just chat
now
every time you color
I like to use warm colors first
still cool
why ask this
Anyway, only blue and red
you just go with the feeling
which would you choose
All right
if you have to ask
that must be
I see
yes
because I like it
you like
sunset eyes
Why on earth are you asking this?
because
you will be right
The generating units of the Yellow River Station are connected to the grid to generate electricity normally
Already connected to the high-altitude transfer station power system
Secondary nuclear power plant switched to full power operation
what happens
Program update detected
Anyway it is
The ladder enters the counterweight adjustment state
you saved us
Central axis main grid equipment is running normally
The power distribution system of each loop is responding
Yellow River station thruster ignition work
The operating track is changed until the sub-nuclear power plant is off track
Hydraulic brake system unlocked
Nanofilaments are about to be released
Very good
we bet right
Worthy of being a Wallfacer
He did it
chairman
The quantum body's shield begins to shift
Low-altitude station safety system overwrite complete
Immediately unlock the low-altitude station
receive
The dock platform starts to unlock
The cabin pressure has been balanced
System-wide self-test completed
Rescue 4 is ready
Can you see where my spacesuit is?
come back soon
immediately
can see
wait for me
Luo Ji
what's wrong i'm here
The quantum body seems to be approaching
you have to come back quickly
What did you say
alarm
Failure of the hydraulic brake system
Nanofilaments cannot be released
Level 1 Disaster Alert
Nanowire turbine chamber about to break
The quantum body seems to be changing
Can Luo Ji hear you?
Level 1 Disaster Alert
High altitude station damaged
Nanowire turbine chamber about to break
what the hell
Zhuang Yan
Did you hear it
Luo Ji
come back quickly
how come this time
Failed to enable safe disassembly mode
We can't both get in
The main structure of the high-altitude transfer station is about to be damaged
I'll go up and see
don't be afraid
wait for me
What's wrong
Electromagnetic Disorder Detected
Can't go up
satellite detected
The sub-nuclear power plant has not yet de-orbited
but has stopped
do not know why
Ding Yi
How can the quantum body get stuck?
Quantum bodies only move with magnetic fields
It's a problem with the counterweight station
It's an engine room problem.
engine room
what happened
I thought the explosion only damaged the outer ring and trusses
It seems that the nanowires can't be released normally.
Wang Miao
Don't be kidding me at this juncture
I'm not in the mood to joke
The pull of the Yellow River Station has continued
Nanofilament can withstand
The engine room can't stand it
Aviation construction materials
There is also a tensile stress threshold
tear it down like this
The ladder is falling apart
It would be better if the ladder could disintegrate safely
But now the combined force of the nanowire and the engine room
Fear of tearing the structure
In case the high-altitude station explodes due to the difference in air pressure
Professor Naro
Warning Ladder counterweight process was forced to abort
Abnormal release of nanofilaments
Ask the second-level engineer to go to the nanowire turbine room immediately
Manual troubleshooting
Abnormal increase in ionizing radiation detected
Abnormal increase in magnetic field strength
Zhuang Yan
can you wait for me
Please confirm whether you are in a non-safe area
I can't ignore
Otherwise we will both die here
Did you hear that
Zhuang Yan
The current body temperature is detected to be 37.6°C
Heart rate 168 beats per minute
Please confirm whether an unconventional extravehicular activity is taking place
Is it in an unsafe area
Alarm detects air leak and depressurization of extravehicular spacesuit
Please take security measures now
Alarm oxygen remaining 65%
Alarm 58% of oxygen remaining
if time could stop
one more second
or successfully leave
either
Diffusion Acceleration
because he faced
is something we can't imagine