<—“Shadow
Elf
They say this quantum state stuff
Will cover here soon
what should we do
The only possibility is
keep it away from us
quick
go to the console
Activated the nuclear power plant at the top of the ladder
quantum body will be attracted
we succeeded
alarm
Failure of the hydraulic brake system
The main structure of the high-altitude transfer station is about to be damaged
Alarm oxygen remaining 65%
alarm
Air leak and depressurization detected in extravehicular spacesuit
Please take security measures now
alarm
Oxygen remaining 55%
Oxygen remaining 48%
it should be this
Ding Yi
what happens when they are put together
or successfully leave
either
Diffusion Acceleration
chairman
What about the ladder base and low altitude station that day
just in case
he once asked me
alarm
Energy margin 9%
Do you have no confidence in him?
i didn't answer directly
alarm
Energy margin 8%
honestly
I was also shaken
but now i have confidence
alarm
Energy margin 7%
because he faced
is something we can't imagine
alarm
Energy margin 6%
still come this far
If a Wallfacer can die and come back to life
alarm
Energy surplus 5%
The wall plan can also
alarm
Energy margin 3%
The quantum body's shield begins to shift
go up
take that kid back
Gravity strikes again
So fast
i got it
Are you OK
Zhuang Yan
Squeeze the door compartment anti-precaution bar railing anti-grab
Fixed location, looking for nearby staff
Paralyzed system force heavy ring one air high alarm
Alert to those who have been enclosed within the E-ring and the F-ring
get out of the way
Start self-help and mutual aid now
back and forth
be patient
Keep calm and keep people trapped
run fast don't stop
Oxygen hypothermia
Access to emergency supplies and reserves
What's the matter?
Stay and do not ask people to know what they know Ring F Road Ring E
Ah, rescuers are injured
risk risk safety
pressure loss temperature loss ring F
Damaged structure Main Port Lichong II Ring 1 Sky High Alarm
I'm throwing away
to seal
Luo Ji
can you hear me
Visual enhancements enabled
Luo Ji
Luo Ji, can you hear me?
I just had a dream
everything in the dream
all so real
but i can't find you
don’t worry
I'm here
no matter which time and space
no matter how many possibilities
you will come back to me
like now
because you risked so much for me
maybe my happiness
really part of your plan
Is it right
I want to give you all the happiness and happiness
if time could stop
one more second
one second is enough
Electromagnetic wave readings appear
The shield is migrating upwards
The high-altitude station signal can be found
Where is the quantum body?
Follow the sub-nuclear power plant
went to deep space
Are Wallfacers safe?
Searching for spacesuit signals
Need not
i saw them
This kid is so lucky
Actually passed between two quantum bodies
only in your eyes
I just feel that the universe has another side
I feel time and space
collapse on us
The sea of ​​stars is vibrating
all of this
All drowned in the light of love's creation
The night sky is a black sphere
Innumerable silver stars
there
is the world we live in
Many mountains like Daxinganling
to all around
extend far
This may be the sunset of mankind
But I remember in Qijiatun
when it's dark
Sometimes someone lights a lamp
don't be afraid
dark is soft
the light of the charcoal fire
how pretty