After 400 years, the three-body talent will arrive
before that
live happily
live on your own terms
This is responsible for yourself
These two big living people can't stand it
Nothing will happen to him or Zhuang Yan
Thank you Mr. Luo Ji
I will remember the starry sky tonight
von neumann
Frederick Taylor's Wall Breaker
The B436 project experiment has come a long way
I advise you
Enough is enough
We just want to observe the energy redundancy after the ball flash attack
absolutely okay
Who's in charge here?
mr taylor
I
is your wall breaker
call the guard
kick him out
Monitor ball flash recovery progress
Remote display that Ghost 1 has locked the position of the ball flash
The ball flash was captured successfully
Recycling program is working fine
thank you sir
won't take long
Are you planning to create a
A space army armed with ball lightning
Is it right
pity
no one alive inside
Are you crazy
How could there be people on the target ship
Troubleshooting tracks
Start the return journey
receive
Thanks
last ground experiment
real target
Not that black obelisk
although it is beautiful
but you don't care
I noticed
Your sight is always intentional or unintentional
sweep those sheep
certainly
Yes
they are everywhere
but you're actually paying attention to their behavior
so that these are everywhere in the desert steppe
know nothing about vertebrates except eating
stay active near the target area
leave it alone
advanced laboratory
Then under your ingenious arrangement
Struck by ball lightning with modified spectrum
in the form of a quantum state
wall over wall
like a real accident
appear in the target area
so the sheep
Or
The quantum sheep attracted by the residual magnetic field
is your real goal
And that expensive black brick
And your anger at Dr. Elena
just come and hold me back
It's just a decoration for your scheme
your imagination is rich
but my enemy is your lord
not a sheep
Of course
So you visited Dr. Ding Yi again
elena is too young
lack of experience in space operations
I still hope
you can be my experiment leader
But you don't care about Ding Yi's reply
what do you want to inquire about
It is in the B436 experiment
Secret Records on Spectrum
and that
In experiments many years ago
woman who was declared dead
start recording
7 o'clock sharp
Instrument calibration complete
please confirm
Who is speaking
you won't answer idiot bogg's question
It doesn't matter who that voice is
How she "died" matters
almost time
Allow me to summarize your thinking
first
sheep hit outside target area
Ear tags are miles away
You are satisfied with the result
It can be seen that as long as the spectrum modulation of the ball flash is accurate
Organisms can not only be hit with precision
also in a quantum state invisible to the naked eye
survive for a while
And the handwriting that appeared after the woman's death proves that
Human beings can not only be quantized
also likely to retain self-awareness
even to some extent
impact our macrocosm
You abandoned morality to defeat the three-body problem
it's not easy
I express my sincere admiration
but also remind you
this
is murdering
War is a kind of killing
No
i mean kill your kind
i didn't kill anyone
you will kill soon
alarm
The base system is paralyzed
Ball lightning recovery procedure tampered with
Please troubleshoot immediately
Our communication system with the outside world has also been interrupted.
correct
Now the spectrum of the ball flash
It has been precisely matched with the human body
spectrum
What is this
This is a masterpiece just for you
Recycling process is automatic
panic what
restart the system
Contact PDC immediately
ok mr taylor
don't worry
four centuries is not long
in human history
not too soon
In the morning of the doomsday war
you can imagine
An average Space Force wakes up early
Hide a yellowed photo in a battle suit
this decisive battle
He has been waiting for nearly a hundred years
Additional load released
lead time path
Limit speed increased by 63.16%
finally came to an end
The night sky is gradually lit up by battleships
intuition told him
the battle begins
control center please answer
Ghost 1
Moving towards the ladder
please answer
Call Experiment Center
Ghost 1 has deviated 4 kilometers
can you hear
He took off in a battleship
In front of you is where all the soldiers meet
fire and blood
will shine here
he swears by it
his child is waiting for him
Long hibernation caused him to miss his parents' funeral
He doesn't want to miss his daughter's
target acceleration too high
It is recommended to suspend the docking order
ignore suggestion
Sudden
A beam of light hit his battleship
Butt fit 43%
Unable to complete docking
last he saw
are countless blue suns
you call it
ball lightning
Butt fit 57%
his last thought
Butt fit 72%
Did your comrades attack you?
Can he return to his daughter?
Butt fit 93%
Butt fit 100%
Docking completed
but these problems
won't get an answer
he them
cabin damage
Countless flesh and blood bodies instantly became human ghosts in the quantum state
Please fix it ASAP
give up docking
Measure the speed of the target ship
Now
They are real heroes
they finally
invincible
Restart to complete the restoration of some system modules
Delayed data just received
Backup catcher is artificially activated
yes
Dr Elena
she is driving
Where is the ball flashing
About to enter the track where the ladder is located
Send a message to the flight control center
No, the communication module is still loading
Progress seems to be stuck
what have you done
did what you wanted
Create communication window
Contact Elena
what's going on
Possibly trying to crash the runaway ship #1 back into orbit
but we can't do it remotely
can't connect
I can't send any commands
Send someone to chase
What are you talking about?
she seems
sailing the last boat
all of these
It's not because you don't have an Ayutthaya
The target ship yaws by 0.08.
but because
you are too arrogant
but
Lord doesn't care
B436 base
desert by the road
throw it out
that button
you
force her to throw
cheer up mr taylor
Anyway, no more experiments
you don't need her
Or
you never needed her
staff please note
The N31 capsule returning to the surface
Arriving at the first ring track platform
Please go to the platform to prepare for boarding
The inspection of the E ring road is almost finished, no problem
Batch D3421 has been inspected, don't worry
I know I'm unreliable in your eyes
but
I'm sorry
there is something i must give you
accept it or not
I was afraid of letting you go
i will regret forever
No
you have given me enough
Zhuang Yan
No
nothing else
but
but this
I
alarm
Damaged solar cell wings
Insufficient power supply
Ladder track position deviation increased
alarm
what happened
Well No. 1 in Gaokong First Ring was hit
run fast
The outer wall structure of cabin d is broken down
chief dispatcher
Both the solar cell wing and the ring were hit
Another panic
The 1d compartment of the first ring was broken down
Gravity Port 2 has a flammable warehouse
Call for emergency assistance on nearby ring roads
The second ring dispatch received
I'm going to call someone
Is the fiber optic terminal damaged?
can't send anything
Central Axis Rail Station Emergency Lock
All cabins are out of service
full assembly
Check Exoskeleton Status
Enable visual enhancements
Locate the damaged point at any time
hurry up
keep up
Axial control center damage
Counterweight adjustment procedure aborted
Ask the second-level engineer to repair immediately
I'm chief dispatcher scott
I ask everyone in the ring to perform an emergency evacuation
The first-level emergency response plan has been activated
All emergency shelters and escape pods are open
emergency exit blocked
repeat
ring everyone
It's too late to evacuate, help!
Follow the evacuation signs
perform an emergency evacuation
How are you
Are you injured?
And you
I'm fine
What's going on here
What happened
Can you get up?
let's get out of here
grab the safety rope
help
alarm
Damage to the main structure of the No. 2 Gravity Port in Gaokong Yihuan was detected
Severe loss of pressure in part of the first ring
All lanes will be closed
Warning all cabins are about to be closed
All personnel on High-altitude First Ring Road G Ring Road H Ring Road
Immediately evacuate toward the I Ring
alarm
The main structure of the No. 2 gravity port in the high-altitude ring is damaged
Loss of temperature and pressure in the F ring
shelter ahead
There is a major security risk
It's going to be sealed
All personnel on the E ring road and the F ring road should not stay
don't leave me
Evacuate immediately towards Ring D
All cabins are being closed
There are wounded rescuers
In the process of hedging
Beware of stepping on and squeezing the hatch
what's going on over there
don't stand still and run
alarm
get out of the way
The main structure of the No. 2 gravity port in the high-altitude ring is damaged
don't come back there
Loss of temperature and pressure in the F ring
There is a major security risk
All personnel on the E ring road and the F ring road should not stay
Why are you standing there? Run away!
where is the shelter
is in front
alarm
People who have been enclosed in the E ring road F ring road
run fast
Walk
Start self-help and mutual aid now
Get nearby emergency supplies
open the door
let's go
Beware of hypothermia and hypoxia
run fast
Those trapped please keep calm
front door fast
patiently waiting for help
run fast
quick
bow your head
go in
Luo Ji
don't close the door
Enzyme
soil=r—1
All emergency shelters on BC D Ring Road are open
open the door
The escape pods are all unlocked
Step aside
All personnel evacuate quickly
orderly evacuation
open the door
Warning that the high-altitude ring gravity system is about to be paralyzed
All personnel are ready for weightlessness and anti-collision
The explosion of the truss of the high-altitude station was monitored
All communication is cut off
What about the data of the aerospace measurement and control network?
Call them all out
Ladder track position deviation increased
Find a space-based observing system
I want more accurate track data
chairman
The sky ladder high-altitude station was hit
The situation is more serious
alright
what do you want to say
Broken website reveals Mr Taylor's plans
millions of words
So fast
block message
go to the flight control center now
receive
Get in touch with Mr. Taylor's lab as soon as possible.
clear
The second team is about to arrive at the traffic hall
go first with extravehicular tools
gas composition analyzer
receive
quick
send to dr.
We need to get to the flight control center immediately
quickly sign
I go to the next one
pay on delivery
Yeah
hurry up
do you want something
I'll let it go
Automatic debit
Buckle up
don’t worry
the data inside
we are fully recovered
same as i thought
Your judgment is basically accurate
i mean you cut it
and what i think
as clean
I remember when I was in Daxinganling
The same goes for the stumps that were cut down
But the fracture is much rougher
Seems like flying blade is pretty powerful
your solar system defense system
Is it ready to build it?
don't ask her how she knows
last question
no other meaning
just to remind you
Humans can't control the power they have
in front of madness
reason
are weak
this
Isn't it just an example?
you
do you have any wishes
such a pity
My time
Running out
Don't worry
Your application to return to Red Bank
UNGA has approved
Thanks
or
Do you still want to visit your daughter's grave?
what i want to tell him
it's over
take care
Professor Ye
i lit the fire
but can't control it
the fire started to spread
i did what i could
Now
It's your turn
Although for them a few light-years away
nothing makes sense
but for me
is meaningful
We can only choose whether to sacrifice
but can't choose what to sacrifice
mr taylor
we support you
president say