Now the spectrum of the ball flash has been precisely matched with the human body
This is a masterpiece just for you
The signal near the high-altitude station disappeared instantly
above
It's like suddenly adding a transparent cover
Ball lightning breaks down the boundary between macro and micro
quantum body
like a mold
Infected our macrocosm
once it starts expanding
The whole space generates what we don't understand
Uncontrollable mutations
i pressed
Listen to you
alarm
Ball lightning recovery program interrupted
Please fix it now
alarm
Ball lightning recovery program interrupted
Please fix it now
be the first to break
you are admirable
von neumann
host
will be with you forever
He faced only one
poor strategist
An Unqualified Wallfacer
you are jealous of him
Rey Diaz's hibernation application
have passed
same with hines
It seems that in a normal life
we can complete the mission
but you don't want to know
Ladder
what the hell is going on now
taylor is broken
But Luo Ji is still on it
I only know
what the lord needs me to know
do not forget
Luo Ji confronted the Lord directly
and
Regardless of ETO
or ordinary human
Lord's Blockade of Microcosms
all thorough
just
checked
The door that leads directly out of the cabin is broken
This window is aerospace glass again
None of the high-speed fragments penetrated
we can't break it
And even if you go out
How to return to the ground is also a problem
Fortunately, there are still supplies left
You feel
Does the PDC know we're alive?
Hard to say
i always wanted to ask
Do you really have what it takes to defeat aliens?
All right
look here
I just snap my fingers
solar system
will disappear
really believe
lied to you
there is no superman in this world
Wallfacer
Isn't it?
If only it would be great
do you think i look like superman now
What's going on? Why hasn't Chairman Say arrived yet?
Ladders are the heart of humanity's near-earth defenses
what's going on now
I heard only one hatch was damaged
don't know
The flight control center does not release the message
It must be related to the broken wall
What about the rescue plan?
why doesn't she vote for us
I heard that Luo Ji, the Wallfacer, is on it
real
that's troublesome
Contact Ronan
ask the chairman how long
Need not
I am attending the meeting on behalf of President Say
no one can replace her
yes
So the chairman must fully direct the rescue.
Other things
she authorized me
The only way is to give up the ladder
Why
Pictures from the low-altitude station show
The high-altitude station now has two symmetrical quantum bodies
It should be what Dr. Ding said
centered on the macronucleus
The resulting symmetrical energy range
But human understanding of the microcosm is too limited
The only possibility is
can keep it away from us
you see
The counterweight station at the top is also a nuclear power plant
Just turn on the maximum magnetic force
quantum body will be attracted
Floating into the deep space with the Yellow River Station
Be attracted
you sure
right
dare not say anything else
but i found
Even if the ball flash becomes a quantum body
The properties of macroelectronics are still preserved
So these primitive properties
can be used by us
for example
magnetic confinement
you verified
In theory, right?
I'm in Dr. Elena's last message
Energy level data for ball flashes found
After inputting the inferred quantum body model
It went through
what does this mean
dna
like human dna
some things never change
Ball lightning can be confined by magnetic fields
Quantum bodies should also be able to
which means
Activated the nuclear power plant at the top of the ladder
is equivalent to creating a predictable
The movement route of the quantum body
In the end, the Yellow River Station will be divided into two
out of part
will be taken to deep space with the quantum body
And the macrograviton fluctuations are not continuous
Once the gravitational pull on people weakens
Survivors have a high probability of waiting until our rescue
Can the power of the sub-nuclear power plant work?
Risk assessment form data is not very good
almost
All departments are doing their best
Verification data has been submitted
this is the only way now
But our fiber optics up there won't work
All wireless signals are lost
The only console that can issue commands to the Yellow River Station
Only the sky station is left
Our spaceship can't get in again
Survivors can't be contacted again
not waiting to die
this thing
evil enough
come out evil
don't keep it
Say it
looking for someone
I have a way
Dr. Ding
we can see above
Then it must not cover the light
strictly speaking
in all electromagnetic waves
Only part of visible light can pass through
buzz
Do you have something that can shine?
The kind that shines far away
Is it reflective?
Solar panels
that became
chairman
Have you heard of the Beacon Tower?
Yes Dashi
A way to communicate with the quantum body
I'm really blinded by you
16th pass
Selected sailboard array No. 5
The azimuth is adjusted forward by 27 arc seconds
Elevation negative adjustment 14 arc seconds
parameter entered
focus target
High-altitude station ring
receive
Altitude station backup power key
46th repeated sending
The relative angle of the solar panel starts to be fine-tuned
Focusing on sunlight
What is the transmission distance
Focal length 16,000 kilometers
Deviation within 50 meters
Make sure you can see the ring road C
I guess it's just those few places where people are breathing.
no problem
Even with slight scattering in the light path
The light intensity is also sufficient
just don't know survivor
How many people can understand Morse code?
i sometimes
also thinking
Been a Wallfacer for so long
you
It must be difficult
yes
but i want to make it easier
That's it
When Michelangelo painted Genesis
There is a small worker to help him pass the brush
pass it over
more than four years
But he says it's the most rewarding job
Because he could never paint Genesis himself
If you can give a little effort to the painter
It seems that I have value
This is how I feel when I meet you
you compare me to michelangelo
do you know how good he is
I know
I studied art history
i shouldn't have brought you up
if not stuck here
I didn't even know the earth was so beautiful
if this is the last view
not bad
Is it right
Luo Ji
quick
do you have pen and paper
give it to me
Oh my god
This is
What
chairman
Do you want to change another way
give them time
hold on
short length is
Emergency energy supply system activated
Temporary restoration of the high-altitude ring lighting subsystem
take a look
is there light
pass down pass down
hurry up
The picture is here
There is a light source at the location of the high-altitude station
Very good
I got it right
is morse code
we are saved
someone is looking for us
we're fine
great great
what's wrong with ding yi
I'm afraid there's no time to celebrate
Not to spoil everyone's happiness
Data show quantum body expansion then speeds up
The distance ladder is fully covered
about
8 hours
you mean
All Ladder Survivors
Including the people in the low-altitude station now
will all die
right
chairman
The survivor area is about to enter the light range
Quick Shiqiang
Communicating Key Content to Survivors
clear
Don't you all want to know the complete rescue plan?
Survivors should be in emergency shelter C1
so that the backup power can be activated
But it's too close to the quantum body
They have to go through the outer ring compartment
move to
Gravity Port 2
back to center axis
when we came up
But Gravity Port 2 has been blown up.
I'm afraid I'll have to go outside for a while.
The sides are sealed off
Subsequent operations require a lot of energy
So you have to find the N48 supply station along the central axis
also a safe spot
Because the quantum body moves up
Make sure not to move here
and this location
minimal damage
But it's too dangerous outside
The compartment is broken like this
It's not as safe as in a suit
and I calculated
Once the quantum body starts moving up
The N48 supply depot will be a perfectly safe location
when they are done
gotta get back to this position
to wait for our rescue
Precautions?
The extravehicular suit is fully intelligent
Everything can be operated according to the UI
only one
Do not enable visual enhancement mode
WTF
Do you understand
I am a secondary engineer
what do you say
Features developed when the ladder was built
Can reconstruct surrounding environment data
but untrained ordinary people
On the contrary, it will affect their normal vision
In short
do one's best
listen to fate
They say this quantum state stuff
Will cover here soon
what should we do
Engineer Yang
Since he can understand
Probably in Morse code too
Let him reveal his identity with a flash
in case of accident
in the last hours
All human beings will remember his sacrifice
chairman
How about it
what did he say
Luo Ji
Wallfacer
turned out to be him
can't be such a coincidence
I'm sure now
great chairman
stop action
Warning that the ladder gravity system is about to be paralyzed
What's wrong
have no idea
Maybe there's something wrong with the center shaft.
your notes
leave it alone
direction is changing
hold on to me first
good
careful
why we stand on the wall
something else floats
Is it a gravity glitch?
No
I'm afraid the quantum body is getting close.
quick
go to the console
We need to contact the PDC
chairman
there is no other way
I think
The chairman is following the wallface act
But which of the bills
Allow us to let the Wallfacers go on adventures?
before he was assisted
You should wait for the rescue of the PDC at a safe point.
chairman
Even if we can find one more survivor
time is too late
Only nuclear power plants are activated
Only when you are safe can you be safe
so without him
rescue plan impossible
but put the Wallfacer's life at risk
It's the PDC's dereliction of duty
we can't take this responsibility
chairman
it's all on
Do you want to let the spaceship enter again?
Engineer Yang
Ding Yi
I go out for a few minutes
you can't
Chairman of the PDC
Don't put Wallfacer in danger
But you can set up Luo Ji's temporary staff
any consequences
i say bear
clear
quick
Is there anything else you haven't told Wallfacer?
to upload
Ding Yi
we live here
hurry up
good
Now the situation is more complicated than before
Quantum body has expanded to a certain extent
The resulting gravitational disturbance is also increasing
It stands to reason that they are inside the quantum body
Using the observer effect to escape is the most reliable
But now Luo Ji can't get out of the shield
Establish a stable exchange of information
His only means of escape now is the extravehicular suit
but only on this
Under normal circumstances, it is impossible to break free from the range of gravity
What about the general situation?
speak English
It's like crashing into a high-speed carousel
Wallfacers have to jump into the gravitational net first
in an elastic collision
exchange angular momentum with it
I see
think of it as a gravity booster
Gain acceleration while turning
yes
Similar to gravitational slingshot effect
Do you have to go in the direction of the quantum body?
why don't we go straight out along the hatchway
It is impossible to break free from gravity directly
Only by being thrown out by force
no
Quantum is too dangerous
It's too late for people to run
How can you jump in?
this is no way
The probability density outside the conscious level is relatively low
As long as Luo Ji passes through there
And fast enough
can avoid the influence of the quantum body to the greatest extent
Jet vector angle 31 degrees
Jet flow 400 per second
Take off according to the parameters I calculated
Thruster parameter setting completed
Do you wear it now?
Tell them to talk through the helmet
Luo Ji called Miss Yan
OVER (end)
Miss Yan received
By the time
There will be electromagnetic interference
If you get too close to the quantum body
This is the effect
murmur
Don't you know that thing is near?
Works better than any alarm
There are many evil tricks
The depressurization of the cabin is about to be completed
Please confirm that preparations are complete
Have the conditions to leave the cabin
Before departure
Be sure to use the emergency console
Open all hatch main doors
Only in this way
to make room for them as much as possible.
space to fly safely
tell him
No matter what sights that subvert common sense
Another I panic
leave quickly
you're not as cynical as they say
and on the contrary
how many people have you met
real
Uncle Shi also said the same
before
It's because I don't worry about anything
not give a damn about
what about now
because
care too much
us
we succeeded
almost
should be soon
catch me
quick
Spatial positioning anomaly detected
The system judges the cross-cabin EVA operation
Enhanced visual mode is automatically enabled
got you
wait for me
Attitude stabilization mode enabled
How are you, Luo Ji?
wake up
The overweight overload value is reduced to a safe range
Luo Ji wake up
Enhanced visual mode disabled
look
they are still alive
Luo Ji
The quantum body seems to be approaching
you have to come back quickly
I can't ignore
Otherwise we will both die here
Did you hear that