Are you planning to create a
A space army armed with ball lightning
pity
no one alive inside
what have you done
did what you wanted
i lit the fire
but can't control it
the fire started to spread
i did what i could
It's your turn
PDC Issues Latest Notice on Ladder Accident
ten days ago
Tianlai high-altitude transfer station located in geosynchronous orbit
hit by accident
after the accident
PDC launches emergency response
do everything possible to treat the wounded
Carry out aftermath work
assessed
The impact damaged part of the structure of the ladder
but did not significantly affect the continued construction of the Spacedock
Ladder project has officially resumed
At the same time, PDC solemnly expresses
The process of human exploration of the universe is bound to be difficult
but we overcome
will never waver in our resolve to advance mainstream defense initiatives
In addition, the rumor that Taylor, the wallfacer, was broken into the wall has attracted the attention of all parties.
The specific content of its plan has aroused heated debate among the public
PDC convenes urgent hearing and makes statement
The Wallface Project must not contain any content that harms human life
Therefore against Mr. Taylor
Newly built space elevator badly damaged
High-altitude transfer station structure torn
Spacedock over 90% destroyed
Massive debris causes 132 satellites to be scrapped
And within 5 years will be on the space station
Spacecraft and outer space activities pose a threat
Debris in progress
Overall progress of mainstream defense plans
delayed by about 18 months
in the accident
A total of 271 people died on the spot
272 people
Subsequent impact is still being counted
It is clear
This is a terrorist attack against the Wallface project
The ETO remnants codenamed "Von Neumann"
must take full responsibility for the accident
No
what he said is true
His fabricated remarks
All fellow human beings will not believe
In the name of the Wallfacers, we have
The families of the victims were properly accommodated
shortly after ladder
will also be fully repaired
the war has just begun
humans need you
mr taylor
my mission is over
president say
I have said in the hearing
I relieve Wallfacer from his duties
and apply
Make my statement available to the world
Can
mr taylor
have you heard the story of abraham
The part on Mount Moriah
We can only choose whether to sacrifice
but can't choose what to sacrifice
This is what you've been looking for
mr taylor
How do you respond to the wallbreaker's statement
Did you deliberately design the failure of the two experiments?
Is it to deceive Tomoko?
Is being broken part of your plan?
Do you feel like you successfully cheated the ETO?
What do you expect ETO to do next?
Do you think there will be new wallbreakers?
Can you publicly refute the Wall Breakers statement?
What do you want to say to the ETO remnants
Is Wallbreaker von Neumann still alive?
After meeting the Wallbreaker for the first time
What experience do you share with other Wallfacers
we believe in wallfacer taylor
mr taylor
Where will you choose your next experimental site
what is your next plan
The catastrophic loss caused by the failure of this space experiment
Is your Dr. Elena responsible?
Brother Luo
someone looking for
who
then wait for me soon
you go first
I just went to my room to tidy up
alarm
The base system is paralyzed
Ball lightning recovery procedure tampered with
Please troubleshoot immediately
spectrum
What is this
It's so beautiful here
like heaven
yes
that's all i have
terribly sorry
we're fine
the past
don't mention it
you are a smart man
even from a certain point of view
Additional load released
You are the most responsible person
Limit speed increased by 63.16%
I
How can it be
At least
you never hurt
people who should be protected
you are right
i came to you
Because only we can understand each other's pain
that person
is it true
he guessed right
But it wasn't this that hit me the hardest
After the Wall Breaker appeared
Broken website made all my plans public
PDC is also preparing to sentence me for crimes against humanity
but they said
the evidence
target acceleration too high
may be part of my strategy
It is recommended to suspend the docking order
I am not charged
Everybody give me that smile
Butt fit 43%
declare the meeting closed
Unable to complete docking
i was completely devastated
I rushed out of the venue
yell at people in the square
i'm wallfacer tyler
my wall breaker
Successfully debunked
my strategic fit 57%
he is right
Butt fit 72%
I'm going to use ball lightning
to attack the earth fleet
I want them to fight as quantum ghosts
Butt fit 93%
I'm going to kill, I'm against humanity
Butt fit 100%
kill me, punish me
Docking completed
The results of it
A large group of people gathered around me in the square to watch
Their eyes seem to say
look
he is wallfacer
cabin damage
he is working
Please fix it ASAP
how well he did
how much you pretend
Breaker
How can we see through his real purpose?
Restart to complete the restoration of some system modules
Send a message to the flight control center
No, the communication module is still loading
Progress seems to be stuck
you laughed too
The smile of the person facing the wall
A Wallfacer laughs at another Wallfacer
You also think I'm working
in disguise
Still executing the plan, right?
How did we get put in such a ridiculous situation
mr taylor
this
I'm afraid it's a vicious circle that we'll never get out of.
I tried
never get out
No
There is a way
I'm here to tell you how
You need rest
rest here for a few days
I need to rest
can i stay here for a while
you are here
can do anything
relax
for a while
I ask you to eat
Brother Luo
Are you OK
No way
staff please note
The N31 capsule returning to the surface
we gather here
for wallfacer
Arriving at the first ring track platform
Frederick Taylor's daughter
Please go to the platform to prepare for boarding
Death of Dr. Elena
offer my deepest condolences
The inspection of the E ring road is almost finished, no problem
Greetings to fellow human beings
Batch D3421 has been inspected, don't worry
From human history to the present
experienced countless catastrophes
We have survived plague and war
and in the ocean
deserts and plains
built an immortal civilization
This bumpy but glorious 3 million years
on a cosmic scale
Maybe just for a moment
but no race
any civilization
can for any reason
small and obliterate everything
we hold dear
so
at the moment we are going to discuss
not just survive
more dignity
The enemy is present
Wallface plan and mainstream defense plan cooperate with each other
alarm
Damaged solar cell wings
Take advantage of each
Insufficient power supply
This is a testament to the cohesion and vitality of human beings
Ladder track position deviation increased
now
The Wallfacer Project enters a period of submersion
alarm
Well No. 1 in Gaokong First Ring was hit
Under the counterattack of the ETO organization
The outer wall structure of cabin d is broken down
Human defenses are being eaten away
human belief
Accepting the challenge
The 1d compartment of the first ring was broken down
Gravity Port 2 has a flammable warehouse
But we are not afraid of the challenge
Call for emergency assistance on nearby ring roads
Because human beings live and die
It's not a mess
Central Axis Rail Station Emergency Lock
but an indestructible whole
All cabins are out of service
the darkest hour
The more we must gather the trust of all mankind
I firmly believe this time
Damage to the control center
of the human victory axis
Counterweight adjustment procedure aborted
Ask the second-level engineer to repair immediately
I'm chief dispatcher scott
I ask everyone in the ring to perform an emergency evacuation
The Wallfacer's Sleep is not the Wallfacer's Sleep
The first-level emergency response plan has been activated
All emergency shelters and escape pods are open
Ladder Rebuild
repeat
It symbolizes that we can conquer all obstacles
ring everyone
Follow the evacuation signs
perform an emergency evacuation
If mainstream defense plans were humanity's shield
then wall plan
by our thinking
A sharp sword pointed at Trisolaran's throat
As the current chairman of the PDC
I will take the survival of mankind as the highest mission
at all costs
Protect our home planet from being violated
will lead you
win this war
Let the approaching invaders see
human beings may be small
but never give in
alarm
Damage to the main structure of the No. 2 Gravity Port in Gaokong Yihuan was detected
Severe loss of pressure in part of the first ring
All lanes will be closed
Warning all cabins are about to be closed
All personnel on High-altitude First Ring Road G Ring Road H Ring Road
Immediately evacuate toward the I Ring
alarm
The main structure of the No. 2 gravity port in the high-altitude ring is damaged
Loss of temperature and pressure in the F ring
There is a major security risk
All personnel on the E ring road and the F ring road should not stay
Evacuate immediately towards Ring D
All cabins are being closed
In the process of hedging
Beware of stepping on and squeezing the hatch
alarm
The main structure of the No. 2 gravity port in the high-altitude ring is damaged
Loss of temperature and pressure in the F ring
There is a major security risk
All personnel on the E ring road and the F ring road should not stay
Why are you standing there? Run away!
alarm
People who have been enclosed in the E ring road F ring road
Start self-help and mutual aid now
Get nearby emergency supplies
Beware of hypothermia and hypoxia
Those trapped please keep calm
patiently waiting for help
Enzyme
soil=r—1
All emergency shelters on BC D Ring Road are open
The escape pods are all unlocked
All personnel evacuate quickly
orderly evacuation
Warning that the high-altitude ring gravity system is about to be paralyzed
All personnel are ready for weightlessness and anti-collision
if this is the last view
not bad
Is it right
but you don't want to know
Ladder
what happened
chairman
How is the damage?
Ball lightning breaks down the boundary between macro and micro
This is impossible
Innumerable possibilities superimposed
What emerges is entirely determined by probability
This issue
come out evil
them
what will happen
don't look back
I can only say
Like Schrödinger's cat that is both alive and dead
Are we underestimating the complexity of disasters?
This is the true face of the universe
everything is uncertain
are filtered out
only see numbers
Coordinate System
so you're saying
The real disaster has just begun